A Guide to the Nelson A. Rockefeller, Vice Presidential records, Central Files, Series 3 FA378
Rockefeller Archive Center
Nelson A. Rockefeller Vice Presidential records, Central Files, Series 3
1974-1977
Rockefeller Archive Center
United States. Office of the Vice President
Rockefeller, Nelson A. (Nelson Aldrich)
FA378
247.2 Cubic Feet
206 standard records cartons -- Boxes 15, 18-23, 25-61, 68-215, 218-224.
Conditions Governing Access note
Open for research with select materials restricted as noted. Brittle or damaged items are available at the discretion of RAC. Researchers interested in accessing digital media (floppy disks, CDs, DVDs, etc.) or audiovisual material (audio cassettes, VHS, etc.) in this collection must use an access surrogate. The original items may not be accessed because of preservation concerns. To request an access surrogate be made, or if you are unsure if there is an access surrogate, please contact an archivist.
Other Finding Aids note
Detailed finding aids for each series of this collection are available:
Nelson A. Rockefeller Vice Presidential Records, Richard Allison (FA377)
Nelson A. Rockefeller Vice Presidential Records, National Commission on Water Quality (FA379)
Nelson A. Rockefeller Vice Presidential Records, New York Office (FA380)
Nelson A. Rockefeller Vice Presidential Records, Joseph E. Persico (FA381)
Nelson A. Rockefeller Vice Presidential Records, Press Releases (FA382)
Nelson A. Rockefeller Vice Presidential Records, Speeches (FA383)
Nelson A. Rockefeller Vice Presidential Records, Working Papers of the Vice President (FA384)
Nelson A. Rockefeller Vice Presidential Records, Foreign Affairs and National Security (FA385)
Biographical/Historical note
President Gerald R. Ford nominated Nelson A. Rockefeller to fill the vacant vice presidency following the resignation of President Richard M. Nixon in August 1974. Rockefeller served as Vice President from December 19, 1974, to January 20, 1977.
File Plan note
Former Classification: III 26 3
Arrangement note
Series 3 Central Files is arranged as follows:
Subseries 1: Name Files, Boxes 70-162.
Subseries 2: Subject Files, Boxes 163-201.
Subseries 3: Chronological Files, June 26, 1975 - January 19, 1979, Boxes 39-48, 58-60, 68.
Subseries 4: Invitations, Boxes 19-22, 49-54, 202-208.
Subseries 5: 1976 Presidential Campaign - Schedules and Invitations, Boxes 209-211.
Subseries 6: Trip files, Boxes 23, 192-197.
Subseries 7: Speeches, Boxes 189-192.
Subseries 8: Vice President's recommendations for federal appointments, Boxes 57, 61.
Subseries 9: Oversized items sent to the Vice President, Boxes 18, 25-38, 55, 56, 69.
Subseries 10: Mail Returned by the Secret Service, Box 15.
Subseries 11: Control Slips and Control Cards, Boxes 212-215, 218-223.
Subseries 12: Correspondence Form Manual, Box 224.
Scope and Contents note
The Central Files series contains the general correspondence of the Office of the Vice President from Nelson A. Rockefeller's tenure (December 19, 1974, to January 20, 1977). The series offers partial documentation of Rockefeller's role in the development of national policy and his duties as President of the U.S. Senate. There is correspondence with President Gerald R. Ford and members of his staff, congressional representatives, senators, other government officials, and foreign dignitaries. However, there is very little in this series documenting actual policy formation. Much of the correspondence with government officials concerns the Vice President's information-gathering activities on behalf of the White House and executive agencies, as well as his support of the President's policies. There are also reports and position papers on national issues submitted to the Vice President by individuals both within and outside the federal government. Virtually all of these were unsolicited.
Also documented here are Rockefeller's campaign activities on behalf of President Ford and Senator Robert Dole in the 1976 presidential campaign.
The bulk of the correspondence consists of letters from U.S. citizens expressing their opinions on issues, inviting the Vice President to speak at events, asking for autographed photographs of the Vice President, or asking for the his assistance in securing an appointment to a federal agency or a military academy. The responses to such correspondence were written by the Vice President's staff.
Carbon copies of outgoing correspondence are filed in the name, subject, and chronological files. Routine incoming correspondence is filed in the name file, while incoming correspondence of significance was photocopied and filed in both the name and subject files. The chronological file contains only outgoing letters.
Presidential campaigns -- United States; Political science; National security -- United States; International relations -- United States; Drug control; Economic policy; Economics; Education; Social sciences; Social problems; Social policy; Public policy; Public health; Prevention and health; Presidents -- United States -- Election -- 1976; Presidential candidates -- United States -- History -- 20th century; Technology; International relations; Veterans -- United States; United States; Water conservation; Vice-Presidents -- United States; Water -- Purification; Water -- Pollution; Energy; Education -- United States; Environmental sciences; Environmental policy; Government policy; Federal government -- United States; International economic relations; Human rights
- Name File, 1
  Scope and Contents
  Carbon copies of outgoing correspondence are filed in the name, subject, and chronological files. Routine incoming correspondence is filed in the name file, while incoming correspondence of significance was photocopied and filed in both the name and subject files.
  - Personal or Organizational - A
    - A (Box 70)
    - ABD (Box 70)
    - ABR (Box 70)
    - AC (Box 70)
    - ADA (Box 70)
    - ADAMS (Box 70)
    - ADAMS-K (Box 70)
    - ADC (Box 70)
    - ADL (Box 70)
    - AE (Box 70)
    - AG (Box 70)
    - AH (Box 70)
    - AI (Box 70)
    - AJ (Box 70)
    - AL (Box 70)
    - ALB (Box 70)
    - ALB (Box 70)
    - ALE (Box 71)
    - ALL (Box 71)
    - ALLEN (Box 71)
    - ALLEN-K (Box 71)
    - ALLENA (Box 71)
    - ALLI (Box 71)
    - ALLM (Box 71)
    - ALV (Box 71)
    - AM (Box 71)
    - AMERICA-A (Box 71)
    - AMERICA-J (Box 71)
    - AMERICA-N (Box 71)
    - AMERICU (Box 71)
    - ANA (Box 72)
    - ANDERSON (Box 72)
    - ANDERSON, F (Box 72)
    - ANDERSON, K (Box 72)
    - ANDERSONA (Box 72)
    - ANG (Box 72)
    - ANM (Box 72)
    - AO (Box 72)
    - AR (Box 72)
    - ARC (Box 72)
    - ARM (Box 72)
    - ARN (Box 72)
    - ARR (Box 72)
    - ASA (Box 73)
    - ASM (Box 73)
    - AT (Box 73)
    - AU (Box 73)
    - AUR (Box 73)
    - AW (Box 73)
  - Personal or Organizational - B
    - B (Box 73)
    - BAD (Box 73)
    - BAH (Box 73)
    - BAIN (Box 73)
    - BAKER (Box 73)
    - BAKF (Box 73)
    - BAL (Box 74)
    - BALE (Box 74)
    - BALL (Box 74)
    - BALM (Box 74)
    - BALU (Box 74)
    - BAN (Box 74)
    - BANK (Box 74)
    - BAP (Box 74)
    - BAR (Box 74)
    - BARD (Box 74)
    - BARN (Box 74)
    - BARNE (Box 74)
    - BARNF (Box 74)
    - BARR (Box 74)
    - BARRI (Box 74)
    - BART (Box 74)
    - BARTL (Box 74)
    - BAS (Box 75)
    - BAT (Box 75)
    - BAU (Box 75)
    - BAX (Box 75)
    - BE (Box 75)
    - BEAR (Box 75)
    - BEB (Box 75)
    - BED (Box 75)
    - BEF (Box 75)
    - BEL (Box 75)
    - BELL (Box 75)
    - BELLA (Box 75)
    - BEN (Box 76)
    - BENN (Box 76)
    - BENO (Box 76)
    - BER (Box 76)
    - BERH (Box 76)
    - BERN (Box 76)
    - BES (Box 76)
    - BEU (Box 76)
    - BI (Box 76)
    - BIG (Box 76)
    - BIL (Box 76)
    - BIN (Box 76)
    - BIR (Box 77)
    - BLACK (Box 77)
    - BLACKA (Box 77)
    - BLAD (Box 77)
    - BLAN (Box 77)
    - BLAS (Box 77)
    - BLB (Box 77)
    - BLO (Box 77)
    - BLU (Box 77)
    - BO (Box 77)
    - BOE (Box 77)
    - BOL (Box 77)
    - BOM (Box 78)
    - BON (Box 78)
    - BOO (Box 78)
    - BOR (Box 78)
    - BOS (Box 78)
    - BOT (Box 78)
    - BOV (Box 78)
    - BOWI (Box 78)
    - BOWM (Box 78)
    - BOX (Box 78)
    - BOYE (Box 78)
    - BR (Box 78)
    - BRAD (Box 78)
    - BRAG (Box 78)
    - BRAS (Box 78)
    - BRAV (Box 78)
    - BRE (Box 79)
    - BREM (Box 79)
    - BRES (Box 79)
    - BRI (Box 79)
    - BRIG (Box 79)
    - BRIS (Box 79)
    - BRO (Box 79)
    - BROD (Box 79)
    - BROO (Box 79)
    - BROS (Box 79)
    - BROWN (Box 79)
    - BROWN - E (Box 79)
    - BROWN - L (Box 79)
    - BROWN - P (Box 79)
    - BROWNE (Box 79)
    - BROY (Box 80)
    - BRU (Box 80)
    - BRY (Box 80)
    - BU (Box 80)
    - BUCK (Box 80)
    - BUD (Box 80)
    - BUL (Box 80)
    - BUN (Box 80)
    - BUR (Box 80)
    - BURE (Box 80)
    - BURK (Box 80)
    - BURL (Box 80)
    - BURN (Box 80)
    - BURNS (Box 80)
    - BURR (Box 80)
    - BURT (Box 80)
    - BUS (Box 81)
    - BUT (Box 81)
    - BUTR (Box 81)
    - BY (Box 81)
  - Personal or Organizational - C
    - C (Box 81)
    - CAL (Box 81)
    - CALL (Box 81)
    - CAM (Box 81)
    - CAMPB (Box 81)
    - CAMPE (Box 81)
    - CAN (Box 81)
    - CANT (Box 81)
    - CAP (Box 82)
    - CAR (Box 82)
    - CARL (Box 82)
    - CARM (Box 82)
    - CARR (Box 82)
    - CARS (Box 82)
    - CART (Box 82)
    - CARU (Box 82)
    - CAS (Box 82)
    - CASN (Box 82)
    - CASS (Box 83)
    - CAT (Box 83)
    - CAU (Box 83)
    - CE (Box 83)
    - CH (Box 83)
    - CHAM (Box 83)
    - CHAN (Box 83)
    - CHAP (Box 83)
    - CHAPMAN, L.E., JR., THE HON. (Box 83)
    - CHAR (Box 83)
    - CHAT (Box 83)
    - CHE (Box 83)
    - CHER (Box 83)
    - CHI (Box 84)
    - CHIN (Box 84)
    - CHK (Box 84)
    - CHR (Box 84)
    - CHU (Box 84)
    - CI (Box 84)
    - CL (Box 84)
    - CLARK (Box 84)
    - CLARK, L (Box 84)
    - CLARKE (Box 84)
    - CLAS (Box 84)
    - CLE (Box 84)
    - CLEV (Box 84)
    - CLI (Box 84)
    - CLO (Box 85)
    - CO (Box 85)
    - COF (Box 85)
    - COL (Box 85)
    - COLE (Box 85)
    - COLM (Box 85)
    - COLLA (Box 85)
    - COLO (Box 85)
    - COM (Box 86)
    - CON (Box 86)
    - CONL (Box 86)
    - CONNO (Box 86)
    - CONR (Box 86)
    - COO (Box 86)
    - COOP (Box 86)
    - COOPER, P (Box 86)
    - COP (Box 86)
    - COR (Box 86)
    - CORK (Box 86)
    - COS (Box 87)
    - COT (Box 87)
    - COU (Box 87)
    - COUNCIL ON FOREIGN RELATIONS (Box 87)
    - COV (Box 87)
    - COX (Box 87)
    - CR (Box 87)
    - CRAN (Box 87)
    - CRE (Box 87)
    - CRO (Box 87)
    - CRU (Box 87)
    - CU (Box 88)
    - CUN (Box 88)
    - CURR (Box 88)
    - CURT (Box 88)
    - CUS (Box 88)
  - Personal or Organizational - D
    - D (Box 88)
    - DAL (Box 88)
    - DAN (Box 88)
    - DAR (Box 88)
    - DAS (Box 88)
    - DAV (Box 89)
    - DAVIS, F. (Box 89)
    - DAVIS, L. (Box 89)
    - DAW (Box 89)
    - DAY (Box 89)
    - DE (Box 89)
    - DEC (Box 89)
    - DEE (Box 89)
    - DEG (Box 90)
    - DEL (Box 90)
    - DELI (Box 90)
    - DEM (Box 90)
    - DEN (Box 90)
    - DENS (Box 90)
    - DEP (Box 90)
    - DER (Box 90)
    - DES (Box 90)
    - DET (Box 90)
    - DI (Box 90)
    - DIC (Box 90)
    - DID (Box 90)
    - DIG (Box 91)
    - DIM (Box 91)
    - DIS (Box 91)
    - DL (Box 91)
    - DO (Box 91)
    - DOD (Box 91)
    - DOL (Box 91)
    - DON (Box 91)
    - DONI (Box 91)
    - DOO (Box 91)
    - DOS (Box 91)
    - DOU (Box 92)
    - DOW (Box 92)
    - DOY (Box 92)
    - DR (Box 92)
    - DRE (Box 92)
    - DRO (Box 92)
    - DU (Box 92)
    - DUD (Box 92)
    - DUG (Box 92)
    - DUM (Box 92)
    - DUND (Box 92)
    - DUNN (Box 92)
    - DUP (Box 93)
    - DV (Box 93)
  - Personal or Organizational - E
    - E (Box 93)
    - EB (Box 93)
    - EBERLE, HAL, HON. (Box 93)
    - ECKERD, JACK, HON. (Box 93)
    - ED (Box 93)
    - EDW (Box 93)
    - EF (Box 93)
    - EH (Box 93)
    - EL (Box 93)
    - ELL (Box 94)
    - ELM (Box 94)
    - EM (Box 94)
    - EN (Box 94)
    - ENG (Box 94)
    - ENN (Box 94)
    - EO (Box 94)
    - ES (Box 94)
    - ESH (Box 94)
    - ESP (Box 94)
    - ET (Box 94)
    - EV (Box 94)
    - EVE (Box 94)
    - EW (Box 94)
  - Personal or Organizational - F
    - F (Box 95)
    - FAL (Box 95)
    - FAR (Box 95)
    - FAS (Box 95)
    - FE (Box 95)
    - FEE (Box 95)
    - FEL (Box 95)
    - FEN (Box 95)
    - FERR (Box 95)
    - FES (Box 95)
    - FIG (Box 95)
    - FIN (Box 95)
    - FINK (Box 96)
    - FINKELSTEIN, JERRY (Box 96)
    - FINN (Box 96)
    - FIS (Box 96)
    - FIT (Box 96)
    - FL (Box 96)
    - FLEM (Box 96)
    - FLET (Box 96)
    - FLI (Box 96)
    - FLO (Box 96)
    - FO (Box 96)
    - FOL (Box 96)
    - FOM (Box 97)
    - FORD (Box 97)
    - FORE (Box 97)
    - FORM (Box 97)
    - FOS (Box 97)
    - FOU (Box 97)
    - FOX (Box 97)
    - FR (Box 97)
    - FRANK (Box 97)
    - FRANO (Box 97)
    - FRE (Box 97)
    - FREK (Box 97)
    - FRIE (Box 98)
    - FRIEDERSDORF, MAX L. (Box 98)
    - FRIF (Box 98)
    - FRO (Box 98)
    - FU (Box 98)
    - FUN (Box 98)
  - Personal or Organizational - G
    - G (Box 98)
    - GALL (Box 98)
    - GAM (Box 98)
    - GAR (Box 98)
    - GARD (Box 98)
    - GARN (Box 98)
    - GARS (Box 99)
    - GAS (Box 99)
    - GAT (Box 99)
    - GAY (Box 99)
    - GE (Box 99)
    - GEG (Box 99)
    - GEM (Box 99)
    - GEO (Box 99)
    - GER (Box 99)
    - GERM (Box 99)
    - GI (Box 99)
    - GIB (Box 99)
    - GID (Box 99)
    - GIL (Box 100)
    - GILL (Box 100)
    - GILM (Box 100)
    - GIM (Box 100)
    - GIS (Box 100)
    - GL (Box 100)
    - GLE (Box 100)
    - GO (Box 100)
    - GOL (Box 100)
    - GOLDE (Box 100)
    - GOLDM (Box 100)
    - GOLE (Box 100)
    - GOO (Box 100)
    - GOODM (Box 100)
    - GOODN (Box 100)
    - GOR (Box 101)
    - GORE (Box 101)
    - GOT (Box 101)
    - GOU (Box 101)
    - GOV (Box 101)
    - GR (Box 101)
    - GRAH (Box 101)
    - GRAN (Box 101)
    - GRAS (Box 101)
    - GRAY (Box 101)
    - GRE (Box 101)
    - GREEN (Box 101)
    - GREENB (Box 101)
    - GREENE (Box 101)
    - GREENS (Box 101)
    - GREG (Box 101)
    - GRI (Box 102)
    - GRIF (Box 102)
    - GRIG (Box 102)
    - GRO (Box 102)
    - GUI (Box 102)
    - GUR (Box 102)
  - Personal or Organizational - H
    - H (Box 102)
    - HAD (Box 102)
    - HAG (Box 102)
    - HAH (Box 102)
    - HAL (Box 103)
    - HALL (Box 103)
    - HAM (Box 103)
    - HAML (Box 103)
    - HAMO (Box 103)
    - HANE (Box 103)
    - HANN (Box 103)
    - HANS (Box 103)
    - HAR (Box 103)
    - HARE (Box 103)
    - HARM (Box 103)
    - HARR (Box 103)
    - HARRIS (Box 104)
    - HARRIS, L (Box 104)
    - HARRISON (Box 104)
    - HARRO (Box 104)
    - HART (Box 104)
    - HARTA (Box 104)
    - HARV (Box 104)
    - HAS (Box 104)
    - HAT (Box 104)
    - HAU (Box 104)
    - HAW (Box 104)
    - HAY (Box 104)
    - HAYF (Box 104)
    - HE (Box 104)
    - HEB (Box 104)
    - HEE (Box 105)
    - HEG (Box 105)
    - HEL (Box 105)
    - HEM (Box 105)
    - HEN (Box 105)
    - HENK (Box 105)
    - HENR (Box 105)
    - HER (Box 105)
    - HERM (Box 105)
    - HERS (Box 105)
    - HES (Box 105)
    - HEU (Box 105)
    - HI (Box 106)
    - HIALEAH-MIAMI SENIOR HIGH SCHOOL (Box 106)
    - HID (Box 106)
    - HIL (Box 106)
    - HILLA (Box 106)
    - HILLM (Box 106)
    - HIM (Box 106)
    - HINK (Box 106)
    - HIR (Box 106)
    - HO (Box 106)
    - HOC (Box 106)
    - HOE (Box 106)
    - HOF (Box 106)
    - HOG (Box 107)
    - HOLD (Box 107)
    - HOLL (Box 107)
    - HOLM (Box 107)
    - HOLT (Box 107)
    - HOM (Box 107)
    - HOO (Box 107)
    - HOP (Box 107)
    - HOR (Box 107)
    - HOS (Box 107)
    - HOU (Box 107)
    - HOW (Box 107)
    - HOWE (Box 107)
    - HOX (Box 107)
    - HU (Box 108)
    - HUD (Box 108)
    - HUG (Box 108)
    - HUH (Box 108)
    - HUN (Box 108)
    - HUR (Box 108)
    - HUS (Box 108)
    - HUT (Box 108)
    - HY (Box 108)
  - Personal or Organizational - I, J
    - I (Box 108)
    - IL (Box 108)
    - IN (Box 108)
    - INS (Box 109)
    - INT (Box 109)
    - IO (Box 109)
    - J (Box 109)
    - JACKSON, K (Box 109)
    - JACO (Box 109)
    - JAM (Box 109)
    - JAMES, H (Box 109)
    - JAN (Box 109)
    - JAV (Box 109)
    - JE (Box 110)
    - JEP (Box 110)
    - JI (Box 110)
    - JO (Box 110)
    - JOHNSON (Box 110)
    - JOHNSON, F (Box 110)
    - JOHNSON, H (Box 110)
    - JOHNSON, L (Box 110)
    - JOHNSON, R (Box 110)
    - JOHNSON, S (Box 110)
    - JOHNSONA (Box 110)
    - JONES (Box 111)
    - JONES, D (Box 111)
    - JONES, K (Box 111)
    - JONES, S (Box 111)
    - JONESA (Box 111)
    - JOU (Box 111)
    - JU (Box 111)
    - JUM (Box 111)
  - Personal or Organizational - K
    - K (Box 111)
    - KAI (Box 111)
    - KAM (Box 111)
    - KAN (Box 111)
    - KAR (Box 112)
    - KAS (Box 112)
    - KAT (Box 112)
    - KAU (Box 112)
    - KE (Box 112)
    - KEE (Box 112)
    - KEG (Box 112)
    - KEL (Box 112)
    - KELLY (Box 112)
    - KEM (Box 112)
    - KENN (Box 112)
    - KENO (Box 112)
    - KER (Box 113)
    - KES (Box 113)
    - KEU (Box 113)
    - KG (Box 113)
    - KI (Box 113)
    - KIL (Box 113)
    - KIM (Box 113)
    - KIN (Box 113)
    - KING, M (Box 113)
    - KIR (Box 113)
    - KIS (Box 113)
    - KIT (Box 113)
    - KL (Box 114)
    - KLEPPE, THOMAS S., HON. (Box 114)
    - KLI (Box 114)
    - KN (Box 114)
    - KONN (Box 114)
    - KO (Box 114)
    - KOL (Box 114)
    - KOM (Box 114)
    - KOR (Box 114)
    - KOS (Box 114)
    - KOT (Box 114)
    - KR (Box 115)
    - KRE (Box 115)
    - KREMINICER, BEVERLY, MRS. (Box 115)
    - KIR (Box 115)
    - KRT (Box 115)
    - KU (Box 115)
    - KUM (Box 115)
    - KUR (Box 115)
    - KURZMAN, STEPEN, HON. (Box 115)
    - KUYKENDALL, JEROME L., HON. (Box 115)
    - KV (Box 115)
  - Personal or Organizational - L
    - L (Box 116)
    - LAD (Box 116)
    - LAG (Box 116)
    - LAM (Box 116)
    - LANE (Box 116)
    - LANG (Box 116)
    - LANH (Box 116)
    - LAR (Box 116)
    - LARR (Box 116)
    - LAS (Box 117)
    - LAT (Box 117)
    - LAU (Box 117)
    - LAV (Box 117)
    - LAW (Box 117)
    - LAY (Box 117)
    - LE (Box 117)
    - LEE (Box 117)
    - LEF (Box 117)
    - LEG (Box 117)
    - LEI (Box 117)
    - LEM (Box 117)
    - LEN (Box 117)
    - LEO (Box 118)
    - LER (Box 118)
    - LEV (Box 118)
    - LEVI, EDWARD H., THE HON. (Box 118)
    - LEVO (Box 118)
    - LEW (Box 118)
    - LEX (Box 118)
    - LI (Box 118)
    - LID (Box 118)
    - LILL (Box 118)
    - LIG (Box 118)
    - LIN (Box 118)
    - LINE (Box 118)
    - LINN (Box 119)
    - LIP (Box 119)
    - LIT (Box 119)
    - LL (Box 119)
    - LO (Box 119)
    - LOD (Box 119)
    - LOG (Box 119)
    - LON (Box 119)
    - LOO (Box 119)
    - LOR (Box 119)
    - LOS (Box 119)
    - LOT (Box 119)
    - LOV (Box 119)
    - LOW (Box 119)
    - LU (Box 120)
    - LUD (Box 120)
    - LUN (Box 120)
    - LUR (Box 120)
    - LY (Box 120)
    - LYNCH, MARJORIE, THE HON. (Box 120)
    - LYNN, JAMES T., THE HON. (Box 120)
    - LYO (Box 120)
  - Personal or Organizational - M
    - M (Box 120)
    - MAC (Box 120)
    - MACK (Box 120)
    - MACL (Box 120)
    - MAD (Box 120)
    - MAE (Box 121)
    - MAH (Box 121)
    - MAJ (Box 121)
    - MAL (Box 121)
    - MALK (Box 121)
    - MAN (Box 121)
    - MANK (Box 121)
    - MANO (Box 121)
    - MAR (Box 121)
    - MARD (Box 121)
    - MARI (Box 121)
    - MARK (Box 122)
    - MARK, HANS (Box 122)
    - MARL (Box 122)
    - MARQ (Box 122)
    - MARS (Box 122)
    - MARTIN (Box 122)
    - MARTIN, H (Box 122)
    - MARTINA (Box 122)
    - MARU (Box 122)
    - MAS (Box 122)
    - MAT (Box 122)
    - MATHEWS, DAVID, THE HON. (Box 122)
    - MATT (Box 122)
    - MAU (Box 123)
    - MAX (Box 123)
    - MAZ (Box 123)
    - Mc (Box 123)
    - McCA (Box 123)
    - McCL (Box 123)
    - McCLOSKEY, ROBERT J., HON. (Box 123)
    - McCLO (Box 123)
    - McCO (Box 123)
    - McCOR (Box 123)
    - McCOU (Box 123)
    - McCOY, CHARLES F. (Box 123)
    - McCP (Box 123)
    - McD (Box 124)
    - McDO (Box 124)
    - McE (Box 124)
    - McG (Box 124)
    - McGL (Box 124)
    - McH (Box 124)
    - McK (Box 124)
    - McKE (Box 124)
    - McL (Box 124)
    - McM (Box 124)
    - McN (Box 124)
    - McR (Box 124)
    - ME (Box 125)
    - MED (Box 125)
    - MEG (Box 125)
    - MEL (Box 125)
    - MEM (Box 125)
    - MEN (Box 125)
    - MER (Box 125)
    - MERR (Box 125)
    - MES (Box 125)
    - MET (Box 125)
    - MEY (Box 125)
    - MI (Box 125)
    - MID (Box 125)
    - MIH (Box 126)
    - MILA (Box 126)
    - MILL (Box 126)
    - MILLANG, RCHARD T. (Box 126)
    - MILLER (Box 126)
    - MILLER, D (Box 126)
    - MILLER, G (Box 126)
    - MILLER, K (Box 126)
    - MILLER, P (Box 126)
    - MILLERA (Box 126)
    - MILM (Box 126)
    - MIN (Box 126)
    - MIR (Box 126)
    - MIS (Box 126)
    - MIT (Box 126)
    - MIU (Box 127)
    - MOL (Box 127)
    - MON (Box 127)
    - MONT (Box 127)
    - MOO (Box 127)
    - MOORE, J (Box 127)
    - MOORE, S (Box 127)
    - MOR (Box 127)
    - MORB (Box 127)
    - MORH (Box 127)
    - MORR (Box 127)
    - MORRI (Box 127)
    - MORRIS, P (Box 127)
    - MORS (Box 128)
    - MOS (Box 128)
    - MOSH (Box 128)
    - MOT (Box 128)
    - MOU (Box 128)
    - MOX (Box 128)
    - MU (Box 128)
    - MUL (Box 128)
    - MUN (Box 128)
    - MURPHY, A (Box 128)
    - MURR (Box 128)
    - MUS (Box 129)
    - MY (Box 129)
  - Personal or Organizational - N
    - N (Box 129)
    - NAJ (Box 129)
    - NAR (Box 129)
    - NATIONAL, A (Box 129)
    - NATIONAL, B (Box 129)
    - NATIONAL, C (Box 129)
    - NATIONAL, F (Box 129)
    - NATIONAL, O (Box 129)
    - NATIONALA (Box 129)
    - NE (Box 130)
    - NEK (Box 130)
    - NES (Box 130)
    - NEW (Box 130)
    - NEWJ (Box 130)
    - NEW YORK (Box 130)
    - NEW YORK A (Box 130)
    - NICHOLS (Box 130)
    - NICK (Box 130)
    - NIG (Box 130)
    - NO (Box 130)
    - NOH (Box 131)
    - NOL (Box 131)
    - NORD (Box 131)
    - NORT (Box 131)
    - NORTO (Box 131)
    - NOS (Box 131)
    - NU (Box 131)
  - Personal or Organizational - O
    - O (Box 131)
    - O'BRIEN (Box 131)
    - OC (Box 131)
    - OD (Box 131)
    - OE (Box 131)
    - OH (Box 131)
    - OL (Box 132)
    - OLI (Box 132)
    - OLSE (Box 132)
    - OLSO (Box 132)
    - OLSP (Box 132)
    - OM (Box 132)
    - OP (Box 132)
    - OR (Box 132)
    - ORF (Box 132)
    - ORP (Box 132)
    - OS (Box 132)
    - OT (Box 132)
    - OU (Box 132)
    - OV (Box 132)
    - OW (Box 132)
  - Personal or Organizational - P
    - P (Box 133)
    - PAG (Box 133)
    - PAL (Box 133)
    - PAN (Box 133)
    - PAP (Box 133)
    - PAR (Box 133)
    - PARK (Box 133)
    - PARKER, J (Box 133)
    - PARL (Box 133)
    - PATT (Box 133)
    - PAU (Box 134)
    - PE (Box 134)
    - PED (Box 134)
    - PEF (Box 134)
    - PEN (Box 134)
    - PEO (Box 134)
    - PER (Box 134)
    - PERL (Box 134)
    - PERS (Box 134)
    - PETERSA (Box 134)
    - PETI (Box 134)
    - PETT (Box 135)
    - PEU (Box 135)
    - PH (Box 135)
    - PHI (Box 135)
    - PHL (Box 135)
    - PI (Box 135)
    - PIF (Box 135)
    - PIN (Box 135)
    - PIO (Box 135)
    - PL (Box 135)
    - PO (Box 136)
    - POL (Box 136)
    - POM (Box 136)
    - POP (Box 136)
    - POT (Box 136)
    - POW (Box 136)
    - POWER (Box 136)
    - PR (Box 136)
    - PRE (Box 136)
    - PRI (Box 136)
    - PRIT (Box 136)
    - PRO (Box 137)
    - PRS (Box 137)
    - PU (Box 137)
    - PY (Box 137)
  - Personal or Organizational - Q
    - Q (Box 137)
    - QUE (Box 137)
    - QUI (Box 137)
  - Personal or Organizational - R
    - R (Box 137)
    - RAD (Box 137)
    - RAE (Box 137)
    - RAM (Box 137)
    - RAN (Box 137)
    - RAP (Box 138)
    - RAT (Box 138)
    - RAW (Box 138)
    - RE (Box 138)
    - REC (Box 138)
    - REED (Box 138)
    - REEF (Box 138)
    - REI (Box 138)
    - REIF (Box 138)
    - REJ (Box 138)
    - REP (Box 138)
    - REQ (Box 138)
    - REX (Box 138)
    - RH (Box 139)
    - RI (Box 139)
    - RICH (Box 139)
    - RICHARDSA (Box 139)
    - RICI (Box 139)